(Raj:)Teams are fun.
(Sheldon:)In that case, I'd like to be
partnered with my good friend Howard.
But I'm always on Howards team.
Ware best friends.
(Raj:)The kind who finish each others...
I really don't think we do the--
Do that! See?
(Penny:)-Oh, hi.
-How'd it go at the mechanic?
(Penny:)Not great.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
(Leonard:)Yeah, sure.
(Raj:)Maybe I can go with you
guys to Houston?
Isn't it late to get plane tick--
(Raj:)Plane tickets? Yeah.
(Howard:)-Will you please sto--
-Stop that? Okay.
(Penny:)I don't know what to do.
My car threw a rod and its totaled.
(Penny:)I can't afford a new one,
I have no job,
(Penny:)and now I can't drive to auditions.
(Leonard:)I'm so sorry.
(Leonard:)I know it's a sensitive subject,
(Leonard:)but can you reconsider
that part in the movie?
(Penny:)I did. I called them.
The part's gone.
(Penny:)They gave it to someone else.
(Penny:)Now that girl's gonna get
discovered and become famous
(Penny:)and go on Letterman and talk
about how she got her big break